Preliminary Guide to the H. Keith H. Brodie, President, Records, 1963 - 1994 UA.03.61.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Working Files for Speeches and Presentations, 1985-1994 and undated
  - Working Files for Speeches and Presentations, 1985-1993 and undated. Accession UA94-8. (Box 3)
    - Trustee Dinner honoring Leon Levine, 1992 Sept. 25 (Box 9)
    - Dedication of Science Resources Center, 1992 Sept. 25 (Box 9)
    - AGB Nomination Letter for Neil Williams, 1992 Sept. 29 (Box 9)
    - Centennial Celebration of Trinity Move, 1992 Sept. 26 (Box 9)
    - Durham Race Relations Forum, 1992 Oct. 8 (Box 9)
    - Christmas Tree Lighting Ceremony, 1992 Dec. 7 (Box 9)
    - NC Mental Health Study Commission, 1992 Dec. 19 (Box 9)
    - Sowers, 1992 (Box 9)
    - Founders' Convocation. University Medal: David Sabiston, Terry Sanford. Distinguished Alumni: Lenox Baker, 1992 Dec. 10 (Box 9)
    - Trustees' Dinner, 1992 Dec. 11 (Box 9)
    - Founders' Society Dinner, 1992 Dec. 12 (Box 9)
    - Founders' Day Lector Notes, 1992 Dec. 13 (Box 9)
    - Founders' Society Breakfast, 1992 Dec. 13 (Box 9)
    - Durham County Commissioners Retreat, 1992 Dec. 17 (Box 9)
    - Martin Luther King Day, 1992 Dec. 18 (Box 9)
    - Address to the Faculty, 1993 Jan. 21 (Box 9)
    - Trustee Dinner. Tribute to Sam Cook. Award to John Chandler, 1993 Feb. 26 (Box 9)
    - Sam Cook, undated (Box 9)
    - Bobby Hurley's Jersey Retirement, 1993 Feb. 28 (Box 9)
    - Presidential Awards Luncheon, 1992 Mar. 4 (Box 9)
    - Reggie Howard Scholarship Recognition, 1993 Apr. 17 (Box 9)
    - ASDU, 1993 Apr. 21 (Box 9)
    - Tipper Gore, 1993 Apr. 24 (2 folders) (Box 9)
    - Golden Apple Ball, 1993 May 1 (Box 9)
    - C. Eric Lincoln Letter, 1993 May 4 (Box 9)
    - Dinner for Retiring Trustees, 1993 May 13 (Box 9)
    - Graduation Letters, 1993 (Box 9)
    - Honorary Degree Recipients' Dinner, 1993 May 15 (Box 9)
    - Commencement, 1993 May 16 (Box 9)
    - Commencement Script, 1993 May 16 (Box 9)
    - Commencement: Mr. Baugh's Script, undated (Box 9)
    - Sylvia Earle, undated (Box 9)
    - William Raspberry, undated (2 folders) (Box 9)
    - Bill Bradley, undated (4 folders) (Box 9)
    - Juanita Kreps, undated (5 folders) (Box 9)
    - Commencement Luncheon, 1993 May 16 (Box 9)
    - Employee Appreciation Week, 1993 June 3 (Box 9)
    - Public Safety Dinner, 1993 June 10 (2 folders) (Box 9)
    - Mezzatesta's Departure, 1993 June 25 (Box 9)
  - Working Files for Speeches and Presentations, 1985-1994 and undated. Accession UA2004-37. (Box 10)
    Dr. Brodie's working files for speeches and other presentations. The files include source materials, correspondence, clippings, schedules, interview notes, and other related materials as well as drafts and final versions of speeches.
    - Current Speech List, 1994 Jan. 26 (Box 10)
    - Previous Speech List, undated (Box 10)
    - Archived Speech List, undated (Box 10)
    - High Point Rotary, 1985 Jan. 31 (Box 10)
    - Speech to the Freshman, 1985 Aug. 21 (Box 10)
    - Inaugural Address to the Faculty, 1985 Sept. 26 (Box 10)
    - Inaugural Address, 1985 Sept. 28 (Box 10)
    - Inaugural Research, undated (Box 10)
    - Inaugural Research & Writing Notes, undated (Box 10)
    - Address to Seniors, 1985 Oct. 28 (Box 10)
    - Preserving the Dissonance: The Public/Private Partnership in Higher Education, 1985 Dec. 6 (Box 10)
    - Preserving the Dissonance: New York Times copy, 1985 Dec. 6 (Box 10)
    - Martin Luther King Speech, 1986 Jan. 15 (Box 10)
    - Martin Luther King Speech, 1986 Jan. 20 (Box 10)
    - Martin Luther King Speech, 1986 Jan. 20 (Box 10)
    - A Psychiatrist Looks at Apartheid, 1986 Feb. 3 (Box 10)
    - Apartheid Speech Research Material, undated (Box 10)
    - Apartheid Address, 1986 Feb. 23 (Box 10)
    - South Africa, undated (2 folders) (Box 10)
    - Address to the Senior Athletes, 1986 Apr. 14 (Box 10)
    - State of the University: Board of Trustees Address, 1986 May 2 (Box 10)
    - Address to the Class of 1990, 1986 Aug. 27 (Box 10)
    - Academic Council, 1986 Sept. 18 (Box 10)
    - Speech Brochure (Address to the Board of Trustees), 1986 Sept. 26 (Box 10)
    - Fuqua Symposium on US Business and South Africa, 1986 Oct. 2 (Box 10)
    - Address to the Seniors, 1986 Oct. 8 (Box 10)
    - Madrid Speech (Address to the Council of European Rectors), 1986 Oct. 23 (2 folders) (Box 10)
    - Madrid, undated (3 folders) (Box 10)
    - Madrid, undated (2 folders) (Box 11)
    - Address to the Faculty, 1986 Dec. 11 (Box 11)
    - Research: Address to the Faculty, 1986 Dec. 11 (Box 11)
    - Address to the Board of Trustees, 1986 Dec. 12 (Box 11)
    - Martin Luther King Speech, 1987 Jan. 15 (Box 11)
    - Menninger, 1987 Jan. 27 (8 folders) (Box 11)
    - Address to the Librarians, 1987 Mar. 19 (Box 11)
    - ROTC Address, 1987 Apr. 11 (Box 11)
    - Address to Senior Athletes, Rennie Presentation, 1987 Apr. 21 (Box 11)
    - University of Richmond Commencement Ceremony, 1987 May 10 (Box 11)
    - Address to Board of Trustees, 1987 Sept. 25 (Box 11)
    - Opening Convocation for New Students, 1987 Aug. 26 (Box 11)
    - Letter to January Freshmen, 1988 (Box 11)
    - Opening of the Center for Biomedical Engineering, 1987 Oct. 2 (Box 12)
    - Address to the Senior Class: Of Pigs and Psychopaths, 1987 Oct. 7 (Box 12)
    - Christmas Truce Bibliography, 1987 Dec. (Box 12)
    - Address to the Faculty, 1987 Dec. 10 (Box 12)
    - Martin Luther King Day, 1988 Jan.18 (Box 12)
    - Durham Rotary Club, 1988 Mar. 21 (Box 12)
    - Conference on Substance Abuse (Reagan Visit), 1988 Feb. 8 (Box 12)
    - Introduction of Derek Bok, 1988 Mar. 23 (Box 12)
    - Address to the Senior Athletes, 1988 Apr. 11 (Box 12)
    - Triangle Area Research Club: Duke University and Cooperate Relations, 1988 Apr. 19 (Box 12)
    - Address to the Board of Trustees: Of Cultures and Anarchy, 1988 May 6 (Box 12)
    - Address to the American Orthopedic Association (AOA), 1988 June 21 (5 folders) (Box 12)
    - Freshman Address: Address to the Class of 1992, 1988 Aug. 24 (Box 12)
    - Freshman Address: Opening Convocation, 1988 Aug. 24 (Box 12)
    - Duke/UNC Conference on Education, 1988 Sept. 16 (3 folders) (Box 12)
    - Address to the Senior Class of 1989, 1988 Oct. 5 (Box 12)
    - Cancer Center Citizen Advisory Committee, 1988 Nov. 7 (Box 12)
    - Faculty Address, 1988 Dec. 8 (2 folders) (Box 12)
    - Alband, Linda: Women Vision Video, undated (Box 13)
    - North Carolina Girls and Women in Sports Day, 1989 Feb. 4 (Box 13)
    - Carnegie Conference on Poverty in South Africa, 1989 Feb. 16 (Box 13)
    - South Africa Symposium Citations, undated (Box 13)
    - Duke Garden's 50th Anniversary Party, 1989 Apr. 15 (Box 13)
    - Senior Athletes Banquet, 1989 Apr. 18 (Box 13)
    - Julian Abele Banquet, 1989 Apr. 21 (Box 13)
    - Project BUILD, 1989 Apr. 18 (2 folders) (Box 13)
    - Welcoming Address to Resident Advisors and Freshman Advisory Counselors, 1989 Apr. 23 (Box 13)
    - Freshman Notes, undated (Box 13)
    - Freshman Address II, undated (Box 13)
    - Freshman Address, 1989 Aug. 24 (Box 13)
    - Opening Convocation and Freshman Address, 1989 Aug. 24 (Box 13)
    - Senior Address, 1989 (Box 13)
    - Senior Address, Commencement, undated (Box 13)
    - Giamatti, Bart, undated (Box 13)
    - Senior Address, 1989 Oct. 10 (Box 13)
    - B. N. Duke Advisory Committee, 1989 Dec. 1 (Box 13)
    - Jabberwocky, 1989 Dec. 5 (Box 13)
    - Alumni Magazine Interview, 1989 Dec.-1990 Jan. (Box 13)
    - Annual Address to the Faculty, undated (Box 13)
    - Faculty Address, 1989 Dec. 7 (Box 13)
    - Martin Luther King Day Celebration, 1990 Jan. 15 (Box 13)
    - Center for Documentary Studies, 1990 Jan. 23 (Box 13)
    - Senior Athletes Banquet, 1990 Apr. 24 (Box 13)
    - Introduction of Herbert Pardes (APA), 1990 May 13 (2 folders) (Box 14)
    - Durham Academy Commencement, 1990 June 2 (Box 14)
    - Country Day School Headmasters Association, 1990 June 21 (Box 14)
    - Deadly Sins and Definitions, undated (Box 14)
    - Country Day School Headmasters Association, 1990 June 21 (Box 14)
    - Headmasters, 1990 June (Box 14)
    - Headmasters: Sources Used, undated (Box 14)
    - Project BUILD, 1990 Aug. 20 (Box 14)
    - Address to Resident Advisors and Freshman Advisory Counselors, 1990 Aug. 22 (Box 14)
    - Address to the Class of 1994, 1990 Aug. 23 (Box 14)
    - Convocation, 1990 Aug. 23 (Box 14)
    - Academic Freedom, N. A. S. Clippings, undated (Box 14)
    - Academic Freedom Statement, 1990 Oct. 18 (Box 14)
    - N. A. S. Clippings, undated (Box 14)
    - Styron Book Review: Darkness Visible, 1990 Oct. 23 (Box 14)
    - Address to the Seniors: Class of 1991, 1990 Oct. 30 (Box 14)
    - Senior Address, 1991 (Box 14)
    - Address to the North Carolina Bar Foundation, 1990 Nov. 9 (4 folders) (Box 14)
    - Faculty Address, 1990 Dec. 6 (4 folders) (Box 14)
    - Closing Statement to Board of Trustees: Academic Freedom, 1991 Feb. 22 (Box 14)
    - Alumni Magazine Interview (Burness), 1991 Apr.-1991 May (Box 14)
    - Presidents Letter to Alumni, 1991 Apr. 3 (Box 14)
    - ROTC Awards Ceremony, 1991 Apr. 20 (Box 14)
    - Senior Athletes Banquet, 1991 Apr. 24 (Box 15)
    - Project BUILD, 1991 Apr. 22 (Box 15)
    - Freshman Address, 1991 Aug. 29 (5 folders) (Box 15)
    - CCB Gold Star Awards Banquet, 1991 Oct. 2 (5 folders) (Box 15)
    - Holocaust Ad in Chronicle, 1991 Nov. 5 (Box 15)
    - Faculty Address, 1992 Jan. 23 (3 folders) (Box 15)
    - Review of In Pursuit of the Ph.D., 1992 Mar. 26 (Box 15)
    - Senior Athletes Dinner, 1992 Apr. 27 (3 folders) (Box 15)
    - High Point University Commencement Address, 1992 May 2 (5 folders) (Box 15)
    - New York Times Op-ed, 1992 July 11 (4 folders) (Box 15)
    - PCAST and Bromley Introduction, 1992 July 21 (2 folders) (Box 15)
    - Indirect Costs, undated (Box 15)
    - Bromley Material, 1992 (Box 16)
    - Research Funding, undated (Box 16)
    - Big Science vs. Individual Investigator, undated (Box 16)
    - Federal Sources, undated (Box 16)
    - Phillip A. Griffiths' Paper, undated (Box 16)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 16)
    - Science and Engineering Indicators, 1991 (Box 16)
    - Address to the Class of 1996, 1992 Aug. 27 (5 folders) (Box 16)
    - Opening Convocation, 1992 Aug. 27 (Box 16)
    - Durham Rotary Club Speech, 1992 Sept. 14 (Box 16)
    - Town/Gown, undated (Box 16)
    - Presidents' Reports, undated (Box 16)
    - Rotary Club Speech, undated (Box 16)
    - Rotary Club Speech Newspaper Clippings, undated (Box 16)
    - Durham Human Relations Forum, 1992 Oct. 8 (Box 16)
    - Letter to President Clinton (Gays in the Military), 1992 Nov. 23 (Box 16)
    - Hostage Crisis, 1992 Oct. 29 (Box 16)
    - Faculty Address, 1993 Jan. 21 (4 folders) (Box 16)
    - Alumni Magazine Interview, 1993 Mar. (Box 16)
    - Tipper Gore, 1993 Apr. 24 (Box 16)
    - Senior Athletes Banquet, 1993 Apr. 26 (7 folders) (Box 16)
    - H. Keith H. Brodie Congratulatory Letters, 1985 (Box 16)
    - Dinner Honoring Dr. and Mrs. Brodie, 1993 May 14 (2 folders) (Box 16)
    - Tribute by Tom Butters, 1993 May 14 (Box 16)
- Subject Files, 1963-1994, bulk 1985-1993
  Chiefly subject files containing correspondence, memoranda, speeches, reports, and other materials. Subjects include admissions, the Academic Council, alumni, committees and campaigns, athletics, The Duke Endowment, various university departments, the Medical Center, and Student Affairs.
  This series is divided into three subseries. The first subseries consists of a number of acquisitions that were combined by University Archives staff. The second and third subseries are additional sets of subject files that were received after the arrangement of the first subseries.
  - Subject Files, 1963-1993 and undated, bulk 1985-1993. Accessions UA95-58, UA95-80, UA95-113, UA95-114, UA96-30, UA96-77, and UA97-65.
    Files are arranged first alphabetically and then in reverse chronological order.
    - Academic Council, 1991-1992 (Box 17)
    - Academic Council, 1991 July 1-1993 (Box 17)
    - Academic Council: Miscellaneous, 1991 July 1-1993 (Box 17)
    - Academic Council, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 17)
    - Academic Council: Agendas & Minutes, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 17)
    - Academic Council, 1987 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 17)
    - Academic Council: Agendas and Minutes, 1987-1989 June 30 (Box 17)
    - Academic Council: Report, 1987-1988 (Box 17)
    - Academic Council, 1986-1987 (Box 17)
    - Academic Council, 1985-1986 (Box 18)
    - Academic Council, 1984-1985 (Box 18)
    - Academic Council, Appendix M, 1984 Sept.-1985 Sept. (Box 18)
    - Academic Council Chair, undated (Box 18)
    - Academic Council: Phil Stewart, Chairman, undated (Box 18)
    - Academic Priorities Committee, 1987 July-1991 June 30 (Box 18)
    - Academic Priorities Committee, 1985-1987 June 30 (Box 18)
    - Accounting Operations, 1985-1992 June 30 (Box 18)
    - Adcock, John F.: Budget, 1990 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 18)
    - Adcock, John F.: Budget, 1989 July 1-1990 June 30 (Box 18)
    - Adcock, John F.: Budget, 1988-1989 (Box 18)
    - Adcock, John F.: Budget Master, 1987-1988 (Box 18)
    - Adcock, John F.: Budget, 1987 July 1 (Box 18)
    - Adcock, John F.: Budget, 1985 July-1987 June 30 (Box 19)
    - Adcock, John F.: Forecast, 1991-1992 (Box 19)
    - Adcock, John F.: Forecast, 1989 July 1-1990 June 30 (Box 19)
    - Adcock, John F.: Additional forecast information, 1987-1988 (Box 19)
    - Adcock, John F.: Forecast, 1987 July 1 (Box 19)
    - Adcock, John F.: Forecast Material, FY 1987-1988 (Box 19)
    - Adcock, John F.: Indirect Costs Misc., undated (Box 19)
    - Adcock, John F.: Indirect Costs, FY 1990-1991 (Box 19)
    - Adcock, John F.: Miscellaneous, 1991 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 20)
    - Adcock, John F.: Miscellaneous, 1990 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 20)
    - Adcock, John F.: Miscellaneous, 1989 July 1-1990 June 30 (Box 20)
    - Adcock, John F.: Overhead Recovery, undated (Box 20)
    - Adcock, John F.: University Controller, 1987 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 20)
    - Adcock, John F.: University Controller, 1985 July 1-1987 June 30 (Box 20)
    - Adcock, John F.: University Operations, 1991 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 20)
    - Adcock, John F.: University Operations, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 20)
    - Adcock, John F.: Year End, 1988-1989 (Box 21)
    - Adcock, John F.: Year End, 1987-1988 (2 folders) (Box 21)
    - Admissions, 1992 (Box 21)
    - Admissions: Early, 1992 (Box 21)
    - Admissions: A-K, 1992 (Box 21)
    - Admissions: L-Z, 1992 (Box 21)
    - Admissions, 1991 (4 folders) (Box 21)
    - Admissions: Misc., 1991 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 21)
    - Admissions: A-L, 1990 (Box 21)
    - Admissions: M-Z, 1990 (Box 21)
    - Admissions: Professional Schools, 1990 July 1 (Box 21)
    - Admissions: Professional Schools, 1986 Feb.-1990 June 30 (Box 22)
    - Admissions, 1989 (Box 22)
    - Admissions: Misc., 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 22)
    - Admissions, 1988 (Box 22)
    - Admissions, 1987 (Box 22)
    - Admissions, 1987 July 1 (Box 22)
    - Admissions: Miscellaneous, 1987 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 22)
    - Admissions, 1986 (2 folders) (Box 22)
    - Admissions Office: Dr. Jean Scott, 1985 July-1987 June 30 (Box 22)
    - Admissions: Director: Dr. Steele, 1985 July-1987 June 30 (Box 23)
    - Admissions: Miscellaneous, 1985 July-1987 June 30 (Box 23)
    - Aging & Human Development, Center for the Study of: 1987 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 23)
    - Aging & Human Development, Center for the Study of: 1985 July-1987 June 30 (Box 23)
    - AIDS, 1985-1992 June 30 (Box 23)
    - Alumni Affairs: Misc., 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 23)
    - Alumni Affairs: Miscellaneous, 1985 July-1989 June 30 (Box 23)
    - Alumni Affairs: Duke Alumni Leadership Manual, undated (Box 23)
    - Alumni Affairs: Laney Funderburk, 1985 July-1987 June 30 (Box 23)
    - Alumni: Class Reunions, 1989 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 24)
    - Alumni: Class Reunions, 1987 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 24)
    - Alumni: Class Reunions, 1985 July-1987 June 30 (Box 24)
    - Alumni: 2 notebooks with info on potential donors, 1986 (Box 24)
    - Alumni: Letters, 1992 July 1 (Box 24)
    - Alumni: Letters, 1991 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 24)
    - Alumni: Letters, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 24)
    - Alumni: Letters, 1987 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 24)
    - Alumni: Letters, 1985 July-1987 June 30 (Box 24)
    - Alumni: Magazine, 1989 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 24)
    - Alumni: Magazine, 1985 July-1989 June 30 (Box 24)
    - Alumni: Presidents Letter to, 1991 Apr.-1992 June 30 (Box 24)
    - American Council on Education, 1991 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 25)
    - American Council on Education, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 25)
    - American Council on Education, 1987 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 25)
    - American Council on Education, 1985 Jully-1987 June 30 (Box 25)
    - American Council of Learned Societies, 1985 July-1987 June 30 (Box 25)
    - American Dance Festival, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 25)
    - American Dance Festival, 1985 July-1989 June 30 (Box 25)
    - American Tobacco, 1987 Sept.-1989 June 30 (Box 25)
    - Animal Rights, 1985 Dec.-1991 June 30 (Box 25)
    - Anlyan, William: Chancellor, 1987 Nov.-1991 June 30 (Box 25)
    - Applicants, 1990 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 25)
    - Applicants for Jobs, 1987 July-1990 June 30 (Box 25)
    - Applicants for Jobs, 1985 July-1987 June 30 (Box 25)
    - Appointments, Promotions, Tenure, Committee: 1985 July-1987 June 30 (Box 25)
    - Archives, 1985 Mar.-1991 June 30 (Box 25)
    - Art Museum, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 26)
    - Art Museum, 1987 July-1989 June 30 (Box 26)
    - Art Museum, 1985 July-1987 June 30 (Box 26)
    - Art Museum: Architectural Site & Committee, 1988 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 26)
    - Arts, Institute of the, 1985 July-1987 June 30 (Box 26)
    - Arts & Sciences Campaign Budget, 1985 June-1989 June 30 (Box 26)
    - Arts & Sciences Capital Campaign Executive Committee, 1985 July-1987 June (Box 26)
    - Arts & Sciences Campaign: Joel Fleishman, Director, 1989 July 1-1990 June 30 (Box 26)
    - Arts & Sciences Campaign: Joel Fleishman, Director, 1987 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 26)
    - Arts & Sciences Campaign: Joel Fleishman, Director, 1985 July-1987 June (Box 26)
    - Arts & Sciences Campaign: Phase II (Campaign for Duke), 1988 June-1989 June 30 (Box 27)
    - Arts & Sciences Campaign Brochures: Various Schools, undated (Box 27)
    - Arts & Sciences Campaign: Major Gifts Committee, 1987 Feb.-1989 June 30 (Box 27)
    - Arts & Arts & Sciences Campaign: Misc., 1985 July-1989 June 30 (Box 27)
    - Arts & Sciences Campaign: NY Prospect Assignments by Staff and Volunteer Breakdowns, 1985 July-1987 Jan. (Box 27)
    - Arts & Sciences Campaign Steering Committee, 1985 July-1987 June (Box 27)
    - Asian/Pacific Studies, 1987 Mar.-1991 June 30 (Box 27)
    - ASDU: Associated Students of Duke University, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 27)
    - ASDU, 1987 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 27)
    - ASDU, 1986 (Box 28)
    - ASDU, 1985 (Box 28)
    - AAU Membership Lists, undated (Box 28)
    - Association of American Colleges, 1985-1991 June 30 (Box 28)
    - Association of American Colleges, 1991 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 28)
    - Association of American Colleges, 1991 Jan. 1-1991 June 30 (Box 28)
    - Association of American Universities, 1990 July 1-1990 Dec. 31 (Box 29)
    - Association of American Universities, 1990 Feb. 1-1990 June 30 (Box 29)
    - 1989 July 1-1990 Jan. 31 (Box 29)
    - Association of American Universities, 1989 Apr.-1990 Jan. (Box 29)
    - Association of American Universities, 1988 Oct.-1989 Mar. (Box 29)
    - Association of American Universities, 1987 Oct.-1988 Sept. (Box 29)
    - Association of American Universities, 1987 July 1-1987 Sept. (Box 30)
    - Association of American Universities, 1986 July-1987 June 30 (Box 30)
    - Association of American Universities, 1986 Jan.-1986 June (Box 30)
    - Association of American Universities, 1985 June-1985 Dec. (Box 30)
    - Association of American Universities Spring Membership Meeting, 1985 April 21-1985 Apr. 23 (Box 30)
    - Association of Governing Boards, 1985-1991 June 30 (Box 30)
    - Athletics: Atlantic Coast Conference, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 31)
    - Athletics: ACC, 1985 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 31)
    - Athletics: Basketball, 1992 July 1 1992 July 1 (Box 31)
    - Athletics: Basketball, 1991 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 31)
    - Athletics: Basketball, 1987 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 31)
    - Athletics: Basketball, 1985 July-1987 June 30 (Box 31)
    - Athletics: Butters, 1987 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 31)
    - Athletics: Tom Butters, 1985 July-1987 June 30 (Box 31)
    - Athletics: College Football Association, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 31)
    - Athletics: College Football Association, 1987 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 31)
    - Athletics: College Football Association, 1985 July 1-1987 June 30 (Box 31)
    - Athletics: Football, 1991 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 32)
    - Athletics: Football, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 32)
    - Athletics: Football, 1987 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 32)
    - Athletics: Football, 1985 July-1987 June 30 (Box 32)
    - Athletics: Miscellaneous, 1992 July 1 (Box 32)
    - Athletics: Miscellaneous, 1991 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 32)
    - Athletics: Miscellaneous, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 32)
    - Athletics: Miscellaneous, 1987 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 32)
    - Athletics: Miscellaneous, 1985 July-1987 June 30 (Box 32)
    - Athletics: NCAA, 1991 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 33)
    - Athletics: NCAA, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 33)
    - Athletics: NCAA, 1987 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 33)
    - Athletics: NCAA, 1985 July-1987 June 30 (Box 33)
    - AT&T, 1985 Aug.-1989 June 30 (Box 33)
    - Auxiliaries, 1986-1992 June 30 (Box 33)
    - Black Alumni, (DUBAC) Duke University Black Alumni Connection, undated (Box 33)
    - Black Faculty, 1989 July 1 (Box 33)
    - Black People, Durham Committee on the Affairs of, undated (Box 33)
    - Black Students, 1986 Jan.-1991 June 30 (Box 33)
    - Black Students, 1991 July 1 (Box 34)
    - Blue Devil: Duke University (Frank Creech), undated (Box 34)
    - Bond Issues, 1987 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 34)
    - Botany Department, 1986 May-1991 June 30 (Box 34)
    - Bramburg, R. William Jr., 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 34)
    - Burke, Dolores: Opportunity Development Center, 1987 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 34)
    - Burke, Dolores: Opportunity Development, 1985 July-1987 June (Box 34)
    - Burness, John, 1991 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 34)
    - Burness, John: Senior Vice President for Public Affairs, 1990 June-1991 June 30 (Box 34)
    - Canadian Studies, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 34)
    - Canadian Studies, 1985 July-1989 June 30 (Box 35)
    - Career Development Center, 1988 Feb.-1991 June 30 (Box 35)
    - Chapel, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 35)
    - Chapel, 1985 Sept.-1989 June 30 (Box 35)
    - Chemistry Department, 1989 July 1 (Box 35)
    - Chemistry Dept., 1983 Apr.-1989 June 30 (Box 35)
    - Chief Executive Officers Meeting, 1989 July 1 (Box 35)
    - Chief Executive Officers Meeting, 1987 Mar.-1989 June 30 (Box 35)
    - Chronicle: Holocaust Issue, 1991 Nov. 1-1992 June 30 (Box 35)
    - Clotfelter, Dr. Charles, 1985-1991 June 30 (Box 35)
    - Cole, R. Taylor, 1985-1991 June 30 (Box 36)
    - Commencement, 1990 (Box 36)
    - Commencement Committee, 1990 (Box 36)
    - Commencement, 1989 (Box 36)
    - Commencement Committee, 1989 (Box 36)
    - Commencement, 1988 (Box 36)
    - Commencement Committee, 1988 (Box 36)
    - Commencement, 1987 (Box 36)
    - Commencement Committee, 1987 (Box 36)
    - Commencement, 1986 (Box 36)
    - Commencement Committee, 1986 (Box 36)
    - Commencement, 1985 (Box 36)
    - Commencement Committee, 1985 (Box 36)